A racing second hand, a shining comet!
عقرب دقائق مسرِع، مذنّب لامع
Conan's logic is good medicine for hearts tired by modern society!
استنتاجات كونان دواء ممتاز للقلوب !المُثقلة بالمجتمع الحديث
Today's stage is a significant hospital room! Find the case's virus!
!مسرح اليوم هو غرفة مشفى مشتركة! لتجد فيروس القضيّة
He sees the single truth for what it is,
يرى الحقيقة الواحدة
and looks like a kid but has the mind of an adult!
يحمل مظهر طفل، لكنّ عقله عقل بالغ
His name? Detective Conan!
!اسمه المتحرّي كونان
"The Robber Hospitalization Case."
قضيّة السارق المنوّم في المشفى
I'm home-- Huh?
رجعت... ماذا؟
Weren't you going to Okino Yoko's concert today, Dad?
ألم تكن ستذهب لحفلة أوكينو يوكو-سان اليوم يا أبي؟
Socks! Socks!
!جوارب! جوارب
Oh, Dad.
يا إلهي يا أبي
Necktie! Necktie!
!ربطة عنق! ربطة عنق
Be careful!
!توخَّ الحذر
Jacket! Jacket! Ticket! Ticket!
!معطف! معطف
And...
...و
...watch your step.
انتبه للأدراج
Please! Drop me off at Okino Yoko-chan's concert hall!
أرجوكم! أنزلوني عند قاعة !حفلة أوكينو يوكو-تشان رجاءً
Today's her last day playing there.
اليوم آخر عرضٍ لها هناك
You broke your leg and you're in an ambulance, not a taxi!
!كسرت ساقك وتُنقل بالإسعاف، وليس سيّارة أجرة
Yoko-chan! Oww!
!يوكو-تشان
Beika General Hospital
مشفى بيكا العام
What a huge hospital!
!يا له من مشفى كبير
That's for certain...
...بالفعل
What room is he in?
في أيّ غرفة العمّ؟
I dunno. I'll go ask at the desk.
لا أدري، سأذهب لسؤال مكتب الاستقبال
He's in Room 503!
!في الغرفة 503
Alright! Let's go!
!حسنٌ! هيّا بنا
Akabane Goemon Sekiguchi Daisaburo Mori Kogoro
أكاباني غويمون سيكيغوتشي دايسابورو موري كوغورو
How lame! Falling down some steps and breaking a bone!
!يا للسخافة! تسقط من الأدراج وتكسر عظامك
Not to mention the cause was an Okino Yoko concert!
!كما أنّ السبب كان حفلةً لأوكينو يوكو
You know you shouldn't rush down stairs.
تعرف أنّ عليك ألّا تسرع على الأدراج
Shaddup. I don't feel like hearing that from you,
اصمتوا، لا أريد سماع هذا منكم
especially since you only dropped by on your way to play.
خصوصاً أنّكم أتيتم للزيارة في طريقكم للعب
You found us out?
كشفتنا؟
Conan-kun's going to teach us to play soccer in the park!
سيعلّمنا كونان-كن لعب !كرة القدم في الحديقة
Then get lost already.
فلترحلوا إذاً
Now, now, Mori-san. Does it really matter if they only dropped by?
هوّن عليك يا موري-سان، أيهمّ إذا زاروك في طريقهم فحسب؟
I had lots of visitors when I first came here, but now I get none.
كان لديّ الكثير من الزوّار عندما دخلت المشفى بدايةً، لكن لا أحد مؤخراً
You should be happy that someone came to see you.
عليك الامتنان لقدوم أحد لرؤيتك
Right, neighbor?
صحيح أيّها الجار؟
He sure isn't friendly...
ليس شخصاً ودوداً
He was carried in here a week ago.
نٌقل إلى هنا قبل أسبوع تقريباً
Apparently, he was seriously hurt in a car accident.
يبدو أنّه أصيب بشدّة في حادث مروريّ
Oh, Yoshio! How rare it is to see you!
!يوشيو؟ من النادر رؤيتك
How's your back, Dad?
كيف حال ظهرك يا أبي؟
Oh, it's much better now.
تحسّن كثيراً
Two weeks in the hospital because of a bad back... how pathetic.
أمضيتُ أسبوعين في مشفى بسبب ظهرٍ متدهور... مثير للشفقة
Are you making sure to take your pills?
أتأخذ دواءك؟
I forgot to take today's.
نسيتُ أخذ جرعة اليوم
You know that's no good. You're diabetic, you know.
تعرف أنّ ذلك لا يصحّ، فأنت تعاني من السكّري
Say, where's Yumi-chan?
بالمناسبة، أين يومي-تشان؟
Did she not come with you?
لم تأت معك؟
O-Oh, Yumiko, she, uhh, you know, went ice-skating with a friend.
...يوميكو
Oh, that's a shame. It would've been nice to see my granddaughter.
هذا مؤسف، أردتُ رؤية وجه حفيدتي بعد غياب
It can't be helped. Yumiko just loves to play.
ليس باليد حيلة، فيوميكو تهوى اللعب
What's yer problem?!
ما خطبك يا رجل؟
N-Nothing!
...لـ-لا
Quit starin' at me!
!لا تحدّق بي
S-Sorry!
!آ-آسف
Say, have they caught the guys yet?
بالمناسبة، هل قبضوا على أولئك المجرمين؟
You know, the guys who robbed your bank last week.
أقصد السارقين الذي سطوا على مصرفك الأسبوع الفائت
N-No, I hear they're still on the run.
لـ-لا، لا يزالون هاربين
In that case, why not speak with Mori Kogoro-san there?
في تلك الحالة، لمَ لا تسأل موري كوغورو-سان هناك؟
Maybe he'll figure something out!
قد يكتشف شيئاً
Hello.
مرحباً
M-Mori? The famous detective?
مـ-موري؟ ذاك المتحرّي الشهير؟
Yes!
أجل
Oh, but all I did was tremble in fear under a desk...
لكن، كلّ ما فعلتُه هو ...الارتجاف خوفاً تحت مكتبي
How pathetic.
مثير للشفقة
Say! Are those the guys from the criminal group
أخبرني، أهم مجموعة اللصوص الذين
that stole 100 million yen and still hasn't been caught?!
سرقوا 100 مليون ينّ ولم يُقبض عليهم بعد؟
That's right. They stole 100 million in broad daylight,
صحيح، سرقوا مئة مليون في وضح النهار
without hurting anyone!
!دون أن يأذوا أحداً
They disabled the security in advance and acted with precision,
عطّلوا نظام الأمان سلفاً، وبناءً على أساليبهم الدقيقة
so their crime syndicate must be quite a large organization.
فيبدو أنّ منظمتهم الإجرامية كبيرة
100 million yen? Could that buy a boxed eel lunch?
مئة مليون ينّ؟ أتستطيع أكل أنقليس بذلك؟
That could buy you anything!
!تستطيع شراء أيّ شيء
Using stolen money is bad!
!الحصول على المال بالسرقة أمرٌ سيّئ
Y-Yeah, you're right!
...صـ-صحيح
How many robbers were in the bank?
كم كان عدد السارقين؟
L-Like I said, I was under my desk, shaking, so...
،لـ-لا أدري، كما قلتُ قبل قليل ...فقد كنتُ تحتي مكتبي أرتجف
But the leader must've said to put your hands up or something, right?
لكن لا بدّ أنّ قائدهم طلب منكم رفع أيديكم بدايةً، أليس كذلك؟
Shut up! If you don't wanna die, hit the floor and stay there!
اخرسوا! إذا لم تريدوا الموت !فانبطحوا على الأرض ولا تتحركوا
Oh, well...
...حسناً
Oh, Dad. I have things to do, so I should be going.
أبي، لديّ بعض الأعمال لذا سأذهب الآن
You're leaving?
ستغادر؟
I'll see you later.
سآتي لزيارتك لاحقاً
Bring a present or something next time you come!
فلتجلب هديّةً وما شابه المرّة القادمة
Yeah.
حسناً
Excuse me.
المعذرة
We're with the police. You're Sekiguchi Yoshio-san, correct?
نحن من الشرطة. أنت سيكيغوتشي يوشيو-سان، صحيح؟
Y-Yes. Why do you ask?
أ-أجل، أهناك أمرٌ ما؟
We'd like to ask you a few things.
نودّ الاستعلام منك عن بعض الأشياء
That man in the bed next to your father was in a car accident.
الرجل على السرير بجوار والدك تعرّض لحادثٍ مروري
Has anyone come to visit him?
هل أتى أحد لزيارته؟
I-I don't know. I only met him today.
لـ-لا أدري، التقيتُه اليوم أوّل مرة
W-Well, I have things to do, so...
...إ-إذاً، لديّ أعمال فسأغادر
My guess is that the robbers probably escaped overseas in a boat.
تخميني أنّ السارقين هربوا خارج البلاد بقارب غالباً
They're hiding out in some mountains somewhere.
لعلّهم يختبئون في إحدى الجبال
Nah, they're probably on a shopping spree with their stolen money!
لا، قد يكونون في جولة تسوّق !بالمال الذي سرقوه
I doubt they'd immediately use the money they stole.
لن يستعملوا المال الذي سرقوه فوراً
Where could they be hiding?
أين يختبئون؟
There's still a good chance the criminal group is nearby.
هناك احتمال كبير بأنّ مجموعة المجرمين لا تزال في القرب
A bank [ginko] robber can only be nearby [kinko].
سارق المصرف لا يبدو أن يكون بالقرب
Get it?!
!فهمتم؟
Let's go.
لتكسر الساق الأخرى
Let's let him rest in peace.
لترقد هنا للأبد
What do you think, Sekiguchi-san?
ما رأيك يا سيكيغوتشي-سان؟
Oh...
ماذا؟
And he was so full of energy earlier...
...كان مفعماً بالحيوية قبل قليل
Did he get tired out, I wonder?
أأصابه الإرهاق يا ترى؟
It wouldn't be nice to wake him up, so our theory party is over.
لا يصحّ إيقاظه، لذا انتهت حفلة الاستنتاج
Aww, you're no fun.
هذا مُمل
Conan. Okino Yoko-chan's on a music show at 3:00,
كونان، سيبدأ برنامج موسيقيّ عند الثالثة تظهر فيه أوكينو يوكو-تشان
and I wanna watch it in the lobby.
وأريد مشاهدته في صالة الانتظار
Could you get me a wheelchair from downstairs?
هلّا جلبت لي كرسيّاً متحرّكاً من الأسفل؟
Sure.
حسناً
Living the hospital life isn't all that bad!
!حياة المشافي ليست سيّئة بين فترة وأخرى
I can't... I just can't do it...
...مستحيل... لا أستطيع فعل ذلك
What's the problem?
ما الخطب؟
Don't tell me you're gonna wimp out at this point?
لا تخبرني أنّك جبنت الآن
A-Are you aware that Mori Kogoro is in that room?!
!أ-أتدرك أنّ موري كوغورو في تلك الغرفة؟
Not to mention there are police lurking outside the room...
كما يوجد رجال شرطة يراقبون خارجها
Forget about the cops. I have that taken care of.
لا تهتم للشرطة، فقد تكفّلتُ بذلك
And don't worry about the detective.
ولا تقلق بشأن المتحرّي
He'll be gone from the room before your 3:30 deadline.
سيكون قد اختفى من الغرفة قبل موعد الثالثة والنصف النهائيّ لك
He's gonna watch some idol TV show in the lobby at 3:00.
سيذهب لمشاهدة برنامج فنّانين في صالة الانتظار عند الثالثة
Those brats are off getting him a wheelchair.
ذهب أولئك الأطفال لجلب كرسي متحرّك له الآن
B-But I can't do it right in front of my father!
!لكن، لا أستطيع فعل ذلك أمام أبي
You gave him the sleeping pills, right?
أعطيته الحبوب المنوّمة، صحيح؟
Then there's nothin' to worry about.
لا حاجة للقلق إذاً
M-My daughter! Is Yumiko all right?!
!ا-ابنتي! هل يوميكو بخير؟
Damn, you're annoying.
يا إلهي، لا حلّ معك
Yeah? What's going on?
مرحباً؟ ماذا؟ ما الأمر؟
His daughter?
ابنته؟
She's having a blast. Should I put her on?
إنّها تستمتع بوقتها، أتريد أن أعطيها الهاتف؟
Here.
اسمع
Daddy?
أبي؟
Y-Yumiko!
!يـ-يوميكو
I'm having lots of fun with a nice lady here!
!أنا أستمتع كثيراً مع آنسة لطيفة هنا
Come get me when you're done talking with the doctor, okay?
تعال لأخذي بعدما تنتهي من الكلام مع الطبيب، حسناً؟
Yumiko!
!يوميكو
Creampuffs
هاك، هذه هديّته
You know what to do, right?
تعرف ما تفعل، صحيح؟
Your chance to do it is before the doctors make their rounds at 3:30,
ستكون فرصتك هي قبل قيام الأطباء بجولاتهم التفقدية عند الثالثة والنصف
when surveillance isn't so tight. Should be simple.
والحراسة مخففة
B-But I've never killed anyone, or even shot a gun before!
لـ-لكني لم أقتل أحداً قبلاً! لم يسبق لي !الإطلاق أو حمل مسدّس بالأصل
Whoops! You'll only rouse suspicion if you shout.
مهلك! ستثير الشبهة إذا رفعت صوتك
Listen. Put the gun up to him and pull the trigger. You can't miss.
اسمع، ضع المسدّس بجسده واضغط الزناد ولن تخفق أبداً
Grow some balls and shoot the guy.
استجمع شجاعتك واقتله
Then it'll all be over.
عندها سينتهي كلّ شيء
B-But...
...لـ-لكن
You still got time. Freshen up in the john and calm down first.
لا يزال هناك وقت، اغسل وجهك في دورة المياه واهدأ ثم افعلها
Do it for your daughter.
لأجل ابنتك
Sorry! My stomach suddenly hurt, so...
آسف، أوجعتني معدتي فجأة
Did you remember to wash your hands?
هل غسلت يديك كما يجب؟
I don't feel like hearing that from you...
لا أريد سماع ذلك منك
So you're certain of it?
أنتم متأكدون إذاً؟
Yes. The tire tracks from the car used in the robbery
أجل، آثار إطارات السيّارة المستعملة في عمليّة السطو
match with the car Akabane was in.
تطابق آثار إطارات السيّارة التي كان أكاباني فيها
Just by coincidence, Akabane is in Detective Mori's room.
يا للمصادفة العجيبة، أكاباني في غرفة المتحرّي موري
Oh? I hear he broke a bone...
عجباً، سمعت أنّه كسر عظامه
Yes. His right leg.
أجل، ساقه اليمنى
Again?!
!مُجدداً؟
Talk about an unlucky guy.
يا للرجل سيّئ الحظ
Anyways, I'm heading back to the station.
بأيّ حال، سأرجع للمركز
When you deem he's fit enough for questioning, haul him on over.
عندما ترونه أصبح قابلاً للاستجواب، فاجلبوه فوراً
Understood, Inspector!
عُلِم سيّدي المفتّش
"I-Inspector"?!
مـ-مفتّش؟
T-This is my chance! He's not here to keep watch over me!
هذه فرصتي! ذاك الشخص الذي !يراقبني ليس هنا
If I tell the inspector everything here, he might be able to...
...إذا بحتُ بكلّ شيء للمفتّش هنا، قد يستطيع
U-Umm!
!الـ-المعذرة
Is something the matter?
أهناك خطبٌ ما؟
Y-Yes! A-Actually...
...أ-أجل، في الواقع
Quit screwing around.
لا تعبث معنا
You heard my partner. You're always under our watch.
سمعتَ من رفيقي، أنت تحت أنظار مراقبتنا دوماً
Any more funny business and you'll be dealt with immediately.
جرّب الاستخفاف بنا ثانيةً وستنال جزاءك الفوريّ
What is it?
ما الأمر؟
Oh, it's nothing. He asked if I had any medicine, since he feels ill.
لا شيء، سألني إذا ما كنتُ أحمل دواءً معي بما أنّه يشعر بتوعّك
You should ask doctors that, not policemen!
عليك سؤال الأطبّاء وليس الشرطة في ذلك
Seriously!
!صدقاً
How long does it take to borrow a stupid wheelchair?!
!كم يستغرق جلب كرسيّ متحرّك واحد؟
Conan suddenly ran off, so we went looking for him!
رحل كونان لمكانٍ ما فجأة !فذهبنا للبحث عنه
Damn you, Conan! You're gonna get a Cobra Twist later!
!كونان الوغد! سأنفذ عليك التفافة كوبرا لاحقاً
Push! Push! Push! Push!
!ادفعوا! ادفعوا! ادفعوا
Oww!
!مؤلم
That's my line!
!أنا المتألّم
What were you doing?! Yoko-chan's show is about to start!
!ما الذي كنت تفعله؟! سيبدأ برنامج يوكو-تشان
You always run off!
تغادر دوماً
Conan! Help push! I gotta get to the TV!
!كونان! ادفع معهم! عليّ الذهاب للتلفاز بسرعة
Sorry, sorry!
!آسف، آسف
It's all you guys' fault if I miss Yoko-chan's singing!
!ستكون غلطتكم إذا انتهى غناء يوكو-تشان
It hasn't even started yet!
!لم يبدأ بعد حتّى
See!
!انظر
I made it in time!
!وصلتُ في الوقت
Hey. I need you guys to do something.
اسمعوا، أريد طلب شيءٍ منكم
What is it?
ماذا؟
Sure! Leave it to us!
!فهمنا، دع الأمر لنا
Just tell her that?
نخبرها بذلك فحسب؟
Let's go!
!هيّا بنا
Hey! Hey! You're not gonna watch?!
أنتم! مهلاً! ألن تشاهدوا؟
I can't do it. I'm up against a wall. No one'll believe me now.
،لا أستطيع، طريقي مسدود لن يصدقني أحد الآن
3:24.
الثالثة وأربع وعشرون
3:30 is the deadline. If I don't do it before then, Yumiko'll be...
...الحدّ الزمني هو الثالثة والنصف ...إذا لم أقتله قبل ذلك، يوميكو سوف
Yumiko'll be thrown off that roof...
...يوميكو سوف تُلقى من ذاك السطح
Yeah. I have to do it.
كلا، عليّ فعلها
I have to, or she'll die!
!عليّ فعلها وإلّا ستموت
He did say they'd take care of things so I wouldn't be found out,
قالوا أنّهم سيتكفلون بالأمور بحيث لا يكتشفني أحد
and I'd only be killing a bank robber...
وسأقتل سارق المصرف ذاك فحسب
Nobody would give a care if I--
...لن يهتمّ أحد إذا
Don't do it.
لا تفعلها
You've been asked to kill that Akabane guy, right?
طُلِب منك قتل ذاك الرجل أكاباني، صحيح يا عمّ؟
Using the weapon inside that creampuff box.
باستعمال السلاح داخل صندوق الكعك بالقشدة هذا
How do you know that?!
وما أدراك بذلك؟
Shh! Don't look at me! They'll notice!
!صه! لا تنظر لي! سينتبهون
How did you--
...كيف
That creampuff box.
صندوق الكعك
Your father can't have sweets-- he's diabetic.
لا يستطيع والدك تناول الحلويات بما أنّه مُصاب بالسكّري
It was obvious something was up,
من الطبيعي أن يشتبه أيّ أحد
given you're still in the hospital with a box that can't be a present,
بعدما أخبرت والدك أنّ لديك أعمالاً لكن بقيت في المشفى
especially after you said you had to leave to take care of things.
ولا تزال تحمل صندوقاً لا يصلح ليكون هديّة
Plus, it's forbidden to use cell phones inside hospitals.
كما استعمال الهواتف الخلويّة داخل المشافي محظور
Yet strange men carrying them are lurking around, watching you.
مع ذلك، يحملها رجال غرباء وهم حولك يراقبونك
Your daughter's being held hostage atop that department store, right?
ابنتك مُحتجزة رهينة على سطح مركز التسوّق ذاك، صحيح؟
You mumbled her name while glancing out the window,
تمتمت باسمها بينما كنت تحدّق من النافذة
and someone there is looking this way through binoculars.
ورأيتُ شخصاً مريباً ينظر إلى هنا بمنظار
I-I've been caught in a trap.
و-وقعتُ في فخّ
I got a call to come here with my daughter
تلقّيتُ اتصالاً للقدوم هنا مع ابنتي
to discuss my father's condition...
...لمناقشة حالة أبي
If you value your daughter's life, you'll kill Akabane!
!إذا كنت تقدّر حياة ابنتك، فلتقتل أكاباني
If you wanna hate anyone, hate the man who just happened
إذا أردت إبغاض أحد، فلتبغض أكاباني
to get stuck in the same room as your old man!
!الذي صادف أنّه في نفس الغرفة مع أبيك
They plan to kill you, too.
إنّهم يخططون لقتلك أيضاً
Immediately after you kill Akabane.
فورما تقتل أكاباني
They're those bank robbers, most likely.
إنّهم جماعة لصوص المصرف على الأرجح
Their plan is to silence their partner and place all the blame on you
خطّتهم هي إسكات زميلهم المُتخلّف وإلقاء كلّ اللوم عليك
by making it look like you worked at the bank as a spy for them.
بجعل الأمر يبدو أنّك كنت تعمل جاسوساً لهم في المصرف
Y-You can't be serious...
...لـ-لا يُعقل
That's the story, based on what the inspector also said in the bathroom.
هذا هو الاستنتاج الذي وصلتُ له بناءً على ما سمعتُه من المفتّش في دورة المياه
The doctors will be making their rounds. Please return to your rooms.
ستبدأ جولات الأطبّاء، فلترجعوا لغرفكم رجاءً
O-Oh no! Three minutes left! I have to go!
!كلا! تبقّت 3 دقائق! عليّ الذهاب
Dammit! Doesn't look like Genta and the others'll make it in time!
تبّاً! لا يبدو أنّ غينتا والبقيّة !سيصلون في الوقت
And I don't know how many of them are in here...
...ولا أعرف عدد الأشخاص هنا
Got no choice!
!لا خيار أمامي
Wow! Creampuffs! Let me have one, mister!
!رائع! كعك بالقشدة !دعني آكل واحدة يا عمّ
S-Stop!
!تـ-توقّف
Huh? There's a gun inside!
!ماذا؟ يوجد مسدّس في الداخل
So cool!
!رائع
Watch out!
!انتبه
That officer, too?!
!ذاك الضابط أيضاً؟
You know better than that, kid!
!لا يجدر بك العبث هكذا يا فتى
Let me go!
!دعني
H-Hey!
!أ-أنت
What's going on?!
!رائع يا يوكو-تشان
It looks like they slipped on my ball!
يبدو أنّهما تعثرا بواسطة كُرتي
Crap! There's another one!
!تبّاً! كان هناك آخر
Yeah? Did it go as planned?
ما الأمر؟ أنجحت الخطّة؟
No! It failed! Take the kid hostage and get--
...كلا! فشلت! خذي الصغيرة رهينةً و
Hey! Hello?!
!لحظة! مرحباً؟
You dumbass! I'm down here!
!يا حمقاء! ألا ترين؟ أنا في الأسفل
Look at the entrance to the hospital!
!انظري لمدخل المشفى
Hey, lady...
...يا آنسة
Yumiko-chan!
يوميكو-تشان؟
Is there a Yumiko-chan here?
هل يوميكو-تشان هنا؟
Yeah, I'm Yumiko.
أجل، أنا يوميكو
So was this lady the person you were with?
هذه الآنسة هي التي كانت معك إذاً؟
She's out cold, but should we tell her what Conan said too?
إنّها فاقدة للوعي، لكن هل نخبرها بما قاله كونان بأيّ حال؟
Yeah.
أجل
"The plan has failed! I'll contact you later! Leave the kid and scram!"
،فشلت الخطّة! سأتّصل بك لاحقاً" "!اتركي الطفلة وغادري
What do you think that means?
ما معنى ذلك برأيكما؟
Him, too?
هو أيضاً؟
Daddy!
!أبي
Daddy! Daddy!
!أبي! أبي
Yumiko...
...يوميكو
Yumiko!
!يوميكو
Yumiko! Yumiko!
!يوميكو! يوميكو
That hurts, Daddy!
هذا مؤلم يا أبي
Good for you!
هذا رائع
I contacted Inspector Megure and told him to come here,
اتّصلتُ بالمفتّش ميغوري وطلبت منه القدوم هنا
so you'll be all right if you explain everything to him.
لذا ستكون الأمور على ما يرام عندما توضّح له كلّ شيء
C'mon! Let's go, Conan!
!كونان! لنذهب بسرعة
Aren't you going to teach us to play soccer?!
ألن تعلّمنا كيف نلعب كرة القدم؟
Yeah!
!بلى
Wait, hold on!
!انتظر
Just who are you?
من أنت؟
Edogawa Conan. A detective.
إيدوغاوا كونان، متحرٍّ
Let's go!
!لنذهب
What happened to the ball, Conan-kun?
كونان-كن، ما حلّ بالكرة؟
Could you tell me what room Mori Kogoro is in? He has a broken leg.
المعذرة، هلّا أخبرتني برقم الغرفة التي فيها موري كوغورو؟ ساقه مكسورة
Of course!
بالطبع
Let's go! Let's go! Yoko-san! Yoko-chan!
!هيّا بنا! هيّا بنا! يوكو-سان! يوكو-تشان
Yoko-chan! You're the best!
!يوكو-تشان! رائع
Mori-san is in Room--
...موري-سان في الغرفة رقم
Yoko! Yoko! Yoko!
لا، لا بأس
No, that's alright.
!يوكو! يوكو! يوكو
Yoko! Yoko! Yoko! Yoko!
!يوكو! يوكو! يوكو! يوكو
Dad!
!أبي
I sprained my foot! Call a doctor!
!لويتُ كاحلي! ا-اطلبي طبيباً يا ران
Whatever!
!لم أعد أهتمّ
Doctor!
!أيّها الطبيب
The Fox is out to kill you?!
!الثعلب يستهدف حياتك؟
Look out!
!انتبه
Those are bullets! Stay down!
!إنّها رصاصات! انبطحوا
Allow the great Mori Kogoro to catch the deadly Fox
سيمسك المتحرّي العظيم موري كوغورو بالثعلب
that's given the police so much trouble!
!الذي سبّب الكثير من العناء للشرطة
Something's not right! There's something more to this guy!
أمرٌ ما ليس في محلّه، يخفي هذا الرجل شيئاً
On the next Conan... "The Traverse of Terror Murder Case (Part 1)."
جريمة قتل تسلّق الجبال المخيفة (الجزء الأوّل)
Next Conan's hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Knife.
سكّين
Next episode's title mentions traversing.
،"الحلقة القادمة عن "تسلّق جبال بمعنى الصعود الطوليّ
It means basic mountain climbing.
المعنى المبسّط هو صعود الجبال